Sheldon!
(Sheldon:)We seem to be moving on
to the annual coitus portion
(Sheldon:)of your birthday
festivities.
(Amy:)Is that okay?
(Sheldon:)I didn't put on my come-hither
plaid PJ's for nothing.
(Amy:)You hate Scotch tape,
but you love Scotch plaid.
(Amy:)You are a mystery.
Guys, wake up!
(Scene:)Bernadette's
having her baby!
(Leonard(off):)Come on, we're going
to the hospital!
(Amy:)I guess... I guess
we should stop.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. I'm afraid so.
(Sheldon:)Childbirth,
looming coitus?
(Sheldon:)This is a banner night
for female genitals.
(Midwife:)Now I see
three of you.
(Midwife:)Do we know the father, or is
this some Mamma Mia nonsense?
(Howard:)I'm the father.
(Midwife:)Okay, Dad, how far apart
are the contractions?